{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Pool Cleaning Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40121/":{"taskOID":40121,"originalTaskOID":40121,"setID":432,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":1511,"questionDisplayText":"Pool type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of pool do you have?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":589,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Above ground","answerDisplayText":"Above ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3182,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"In ground","answerDisplayText":"In ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3201,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Indoor","answerDisplayText":"Indoor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4470,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Outdoor","answerDisplayText":"Outdoor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1513,"questionDisplayText":"Pool materials","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the pool made of?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2427,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Fiberglass","answerDisplayText":"Fiberglass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11529,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Concrete","answerDisplayText":"Concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6354,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Tile","answerDisplayText":"Tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11530,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6711,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Vinyl liner","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl liner","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1517,"questionDisplayText":"Service desired","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of service do you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4386,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One time cleaning","answerDisplayText":"One time cleaning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5108,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Regular maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Regular maintenance service","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7024,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Winterization","answerDisplayText":"Winterization","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":60001,"questionDisplayText":"Recurring Service Requested","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Will this request be a recurring service?","shortQuestionText":"Is a recurring service?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":13,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":1511,"questionDisplayText":"Pool type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of pool do you have?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":589,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Above ground","answerDisplayText":"Above ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3182,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"In ground","answerDisplayText":"In ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3201,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Indoor","answerDisplayText":"Indoor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4470,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Outdoor","answerDisplayText":"Outdoor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":589,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Above ground","answerDisplayText":"Above ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3182,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"In ground","answerDisplayText":"In ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3201,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Indoor","answerDisplayText":"Indoor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4470,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Outdoor","answerDisplayText":"Outdoor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1513,"questionDisplayText":"Pool materials","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the pool made of?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2427,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Fiberglass","answerDisplayText":"Fiberglass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11529,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Concrete","answerDisplayText":"Concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6354,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Tile","answerDisplayText":"Tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11530,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6711,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Vinyl liner","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl liner","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2427,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Fiberglass","answerDisplayText":"Fiberglass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11529,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Concrete","answerDisplayText":"Concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6354,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Tile","answerDisplayText":"Tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11530,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6711,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Vinyl liner","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl liner","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1517,"questionDisplayText":"Service desired","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of service do you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4386,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One time cleaning","answerDisplayText":"One time cleaning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5108,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Regular maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Regular maintenance service","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7024,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Winterization","answerDisplayText":"Winterization","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4386,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One time cleaning","answerDisplayText":"One time cleaning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5108,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Regular maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Regular maintenance service","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7024,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Winterization","answerDisplayText":"Winterization","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":60001,"questionDisplayText":"Recurring Service Requested","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Will this request be a recurring service?","shortQuestionText":"Is a recurring service?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":13,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40121/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40121,"taskName":"Swimming Pool - Clean and Maintain","taskDescription":"Clean or Maintain a Swimming Pool","xmTaskDescriptor":"Pool Cleaning Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":182,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Clean Pool Maintain Cleaner Maintenance","textMessagingName":"Clean Pool","rolloverLongDesc":"Typically handles seasonal start-up \u0026 shut down, periodic cleaning, filter cleaning or changing, painting \u0026 other routine maintenance tasks.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes adding chemicals, maintaining water level, removing debris.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Clean or Maintain a Swimming Pool.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Pool Cleaning Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Swimming Pool Cleaners","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":61,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Clean \u0026 Maintain Swimming Pool","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Swimming Pool - Clean and Maintain","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Swimming Pool Cleaning Project","urlName":"Swimming-Pool-Clean-and-Maintain","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Pool Cleaning Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Pool Cleaners","searchKeywords":"Clean,Pool,Maintain,Cleaner,Maintenance,semi,vinyl,servicies,sauna,material,filter,costs,care,tub,hot,cleaning,fiberglass,ground,above,Swimming,inground,Pools,Cleaners","emcCategoryOid":-12070,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":432,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}